太好了  看这是谁来了
Oh, great. Look who's here.
怎么不再说大点声  你好  斯林[苗条]
Wow, a little louder, please. Hi, Slim.
他的名字还是苗条  真是笑死了
Ha, and his name's Slim. Hysterical.
他是个很好的人
He's a great guy.
何止一个  他一个顶三四个
No, he's three or four great guys.
你要冷静下来
You have got to calm down.
你在干嘛  那是什么
What are you doing? What are these?
明信片
Postcards.
我们还在纽约
We're still in New York.
我答应过孩子们还有伊莫金
I promised the kids. I promised Imogene.
这里是爱德怀德机场  他们搭地铁就能到
It's fucking Idlewild Airport. They could subway here.
你要把它弄皱了
You're bending it.
你们赶上了飞机  这是个好的开始
You made the plane. That's a good start.
Slim Snacks[斯林斯内克]同义小吃
斯林没带斯内克上来对吧
Hey, Slim's not bringing snacks, is he?
什么
What?
雷吉  我们的房间
So, Reggie, will our room